ankle_and_foot_oian_quiz = [
    {"question": "What is the origin of Gastrocnemius?", "options": ["Medial and lateral condyles of femur", "Posterior surface of tibia", "Lateral surface of fibula"], "answer": "a"},
    {"question": "What is the insertion of Gastrocnemius?", "options": ["Calcaneus via Achilles tendon", "Base of the first metatarsal", "Navicular bone"], "answer": "a"},
    {"question": "What is the action of Gastrocnemius?", "options": ["Dorsiflexes foot", "Plantar flexes foot", "Everts foot"], "answer": "b"},
    {"question": "What is the nerve of Gastrocnemius?", "options": ["Tibial nerve", "Common peroneal nerve", "Superficial peroneal nerve"], "answer": "a"},
    {"question": "What is the origin of Soleus?", "options": ["Posterior surface of tibia and fibula", "Medial and lateral condyles of femur", "Anterior surface of tibia"], "answer": "a"},
    {"question": "What is the insertion of Soleus?", "options": ["Navicular bone", "Calcaneus via Achilles tendon", "Base of the first metatarsal"], "answer": "b"},
    {"question": "What is the action of Soleus?", "options": ["Everts foot", "Dorsiflexes foot", "Plantar flexes foot"], "answer": "c"},
    {"question": "What is the nerve of Soleus?", "options": ["Superficial peroneal nerve", "Tibial nerve", "Common peroneal nerve"], "answer": "b"},
    {"question": "What is the origin of Tibialis Anterior?", "options": ["Lateral condyle and upper two-thirds of tibial shaft", "Medial and lateral condyles of femur", "Posterior surface of tibia"], "answer": "a"},
    {"question": "What is the insertion of Tibialis Anterior?", "options": ["Base of the first metatarsal", "Calcaneus via Achilles tendon", "Navicular bone"], "answer": "a"},
    {"question": "What is the action of Tibialis Anterior?", "options": ["Plantar flexes foot", "Everts foot", "Dorsiflexes foot"], "answer": "c"},
    {"question": "What is the nerve of Tibialis Anterior?", "options": ["Tibial nerve", "Common peroneal nerve", "Deep peroneal nerve"], "answer": "c"},
    {"question": "What is the origin of Peroneus Longus?", "options": ["Lateral surface of fibula", "Posterior surface of tibia", "Medial and lateral condyles of femur"], "answer": "a"},
    {"question": "What is the insertion of Peroneus Longus?", "options": ["Navicular bone", "Base of the first metatarsal", "Calcaneus via Achilles tendon"], "answer": "b"},
    {"question": "What is the action of Peroneus Longus?", "options": ["Plantar flexes foot", "Dorsiflexes foot", "Everts foot"], "answer": "c"},
    {"question": "What is the nerve of Peroneus Longus?", "options": ["Superficial peroneal nerve", "Tibial nerve", "Common peroneal nerve"], "answer": "a"}
]
